

Nguyen Thi Hong Tho

Front-end Developer

Date of birth: October 20, 1995

Gender: Female

Phone: 0166 252 4798

Email: thohong95@gmail.com

Address: 19 Nguyen Huu Tho, Dist 7, Ho Chi Minh City

Website: https://www.facebook.com/tho.hong95

OBJECTIVE

I believe my skills and past work experiences make me a good fit for this position. I have been building my skills, my knowledge, my attitude day by day to become a professional front-end developer, contribute to the development of company

EDUCATION

Oct 2013 - Oct 2017

Sai Gon Technology University

Major: Information Technology

GPA: 7.5/10

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2017 - Apr 2017

Internship at Saigon Technology University

Create a news web

Hosting: http://googlenews.hol.es/

Description: This web helps people look up new information.

Team size: 4 .

My responsibilities:

- Analyze the requirement.
- Design database and prototype Review code .
- Design themes of websites: use Boostrap and the knowledges about CSS, HTML...
- Coding and unit testing Technologies used: Sublime Text, PHP, Ajax, Jquery,

May 2017 - Present

HHDGroup Company

PHP Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Developing several functions: update information instantly, send message, inbox, bad news.
- Using framework phanlcon and the knowledges about css, jquery to complete some tasks.
- Designing themes of websites: use Boostrap and the knowledges about CSS, HTML...
- Link: https://www.nhadat.net/

CERTIFICATIONS

| 2017 | PHP developer Certificate issued by Computer Science Center |
|------|---|
| | University of Science |
| | |

ACTIVITIES

| May 2015 - Apr 2015 | Green Summer Volunteer Campaign: |
|---------------------|---|
| | Volunteers |
| | - Clean up all the corners or alleys in District 8. |
| | - Propagate the prevention malaria in Binh Thanh District . |
| | - Build charitable houses for the poor in Dong Thap Province. |
| May 2015 - Apr 2015 | Green Summer Volunteer Campaign: |
| | Volunteers |
| | - Clean up all the corners or alleys in District 8. |
| | - Propagate the prevention malaria in Binh Thanh District . |
| | - Build charitable houses for the poor in Dong Thap Province. |
| Jan 2016 - Feb 2016 | Loved Spring Activity volunteers |
| | Volunteers |
| | - Participate in making Tet cake (sticky rice cake) for children in Cu Chi |
| | district. |
| | - Give gifts to Vietnamese Heroic Mothers . |
| | - Establish a fund for poor children by buying red envelopes in District 8. |

SKILLS

| Language | English, Japanese |
|---------------------|---|
| Computer | My best skills is: HTML, HTML5, CSS,CSS3. Design responsive website PHP language. Javasript, JQuery, Bootstrap. MySQL, NoSQL mongodb Have some knowledge about: Framework Codelgniter, Phalcon Framework -Word, Excel, Powerpoint. |
| Job-related skills: | Communication and interpersonal skills Passion for self-improvement, self-learning and self-motivation. Hard-working, ability to work under high pressure. Skills to work independently as well as collaboratively. Ability to adapt to job requirements. |

INTERESTS

- Reading the magazine PC World.Like to learn science, technology.Travel.

REFERENCES

Trần Văn Hùng

- Lecturer Sai Gon Technology University

- Email: hung.tranvan@stu.edu.vn

- Mobile: 0903762632